<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Cameryn Brock</title>
    <link>/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Cameryn Brock</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography: California</title>
      <link>/portfolio/california/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/california/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing UCSB Campus Profiles</title>
      <link>/portfolio/ucsb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/ucsb/</guid>
      <description>Here we compare the percentage of white and minority students of total UCSB undergraduate students from 2008-2018 to demonstrate how the relative proportions are changing over time (Figure 1). Data is compiled from the annual UCSB Campus Profiles prepared by the Office of Budget and Planning through the Institutional Research, Planning, &amp;amp; Assessment Initiative (UCSB).
This dataset includes graduate and undergraduate students; however, we only used data for undergraduate students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography: South Africa</title>
      <link>/portfolio/south-africa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/south-africa/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weight Distribution for Snowshoe Hares in Bonanza Creek</title>
      <link>/portfolio/snowshoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/snowshoe/</guid>
      <description>Figure 1. Snowshoe hare (Lepus americanus) in its summer coat. Credit: Daniel Dagenais, Canadian Wildlife Federation.
Snowshoe hares (Lepus americanus) are considered a keystone species in boreal forests due to their role as a critical food source for carnivores. Here we will explore the seasonal weight distribution of adults and juveniles in spring-fall. We will use a subset of data from the snowshoe hare physical data in Bonanza Creek Experimental Forest dataset (1999-2012), including</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography: Ecuador</title>
      <link>/portfolio/ecuador/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/ecuador/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Penguin Mass</title>
      <link>/portfolio/penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/penguins/</guid>
      <description>Adelie Penguin (Pygoscelis adeliae) jumping into finals week. Credit: Ralph Lee Hopkins, National Geographic
Here we explored the potential for predicting penguin mass in Adelie, Chinstrap, and Gentoo penguins considering flipper length, sex, and species. We used data recorded at Palmer Station, LTER, Antarctica, compiled from the Environmental Data Initative (Gorman 2017).
Figure 1. Penguin species, sex, flipper length, and body mass. Data was recorded at Palmer Station, LTER, Antarctica and compiled from the Environmental Data Initiative (Gorman 2017)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography: Australia</title>
      <link>/portfolio/australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/australia/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Land Use and Watersheds</title>
      <link>/portfolio/hawaii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/hawaii/</guid>
      <description>Data source Land use: Hawaii Statewide GIS Program. Land Use Land Cover of main Hawaiian Islands (2017). Available from http://geoportal.hawaii.gov/datasets/land-use-land-cover-lulc
Watersheds: Hawaii Statewide GIS Program. Surface Water Hyrdrologic Unit Boundaries (Watersheds) for the 8 major Hawaiian Islands (2017). Available from http://geoportal.hawaii.gov/datasets/watersheds
Attach packages and read in data library(tidyverse) library(here) library(sf) library(tmap) land_use &amp;lt;- read_sf(dsn = &amp;quot;Land_Use_Land_Cover_LULC&amp;quot;, layer = &amp;quot;Land_Use_Land_Cover_LULC&amp;quot;) %&amp;gt;% select(landcover) %&amp;gt;% filter(!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steelhead Salmon Passage across the Bonneville Dam</title>
      <link>/portfolio/steelhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/steelhead/</guid>
      <description>Figure 1. Steelhead salmon (Onchorhynchus mykiss). Credit: Duane River, US Fish and Wildlife Service.
Dams create an obstacle for migrating fish. Some dams have constructed fish ladders to address this issue. Here, we will use data from Columbia River DART to analyze adult steelhead salmon (Onchorhynchus mykiss) passage through the fish ladder at the Bonneville Dam from 1940-2019.
Data: Columbia River DART, Columbia Basin Research, University of Washington. (2019). Adult Passage Graphics &amp;amp; Text.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>